# **GANESH** GADAM SYSTEM ENGINEER AT INFOSYS

**\** 7775006350

Nagpur

f ganesh.gadam.1

in /ganeshgadam

I'm Software Developer having 3+ years of experience in the BFSI domain, I specialize in Finacle and Java frameworks. Recognized for my collaborative contributions within the Finacle Unit, I've been promoted for my efforts. Additionally, I've taken the lead in client engagements, overseeing requirement gathering, providing live deployment support, and resolving issues efficiently. I firmly believe in designing and creating data environments which are fast, reliable and flexible in nature. I'm a curious, persistent and positive learner, with strong technical and analytical skills flexible in quickly adapting to new technology and tools

### Skills

#### PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

#### SCRIPTING LANGUAGE

DEH

J2EE

Spring

Microservices

### DATABASE

MYSOL

Oracle Database

PostreSQL Sql Server

### TOOLS

Eclips

Postmar

GIT Lab

Jira

### Education

#### G.H. RAISONI COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING

B.E. Computer Scien ce Engineer 2020 CGPA-8.08

VANDE MATARAM COLLEGE

Marks-64.4%

SARASWATI VIDYALAYA SCHOOL

Percentage: 75.6%

# **Employment**

#### Infosys Private Limited

Pune July 2021 to Current

Mumbai

July 2020 to July 2021

- Technology Used: Java | Rest API | Html and CSS | JavaScript | Oracle Database
- •Managed and optimized customer engagement channels, including online banking, mobile banking. · Implemented and configured the Finacle banking software for digital engagement hub (DEH) operations.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to ensure seamless integration of Finacle DEH with various systems and platforms.
- Provided training and ongoing support to bank employees on utilizing Finacle DEH effectively.
- Develop endpoints for consuming and orchestrating data between web-application and micro-services
- Analysed customer behaviour and feedback to improve digital banking services and enhance customer experience.

#### Simplified Financial Solutions Private Limited (1 PAY)

Software DeveloperTechnology - JAVA | JSP | HTML | CSS | MYSQL

Client - HDFC Bank

- · Utilized Java, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, MySQL, and Servlet technologies in the development process.
- Developed applications tailored for Indian Oil Petroleum.
- These applications facilitate corporate customers' payments to Indian Oil Petroleum.
- · Various modules were incorporated into the application, including Add Card Details, Transaction History, and a Maker-Checker system.
- Designed and implemented an application for Electronic Cash Management Services (ECMS).
- · Within the ECMS application, customers make offline payments to the bank.
- · Offline payment methods supported include NEFT/RTGS, cash, cheques, and demand drafts.
- · To make an offline payment, customers must download a Challan and submit it to the bank before the expiry date

## Simplified Financial Solutions Private Limited (1 PAY)

Mumbai Nov. 2019 to May 2020

• Technology Used: Java | Html and CSS | JavaScript | MySQL | Servlet

- Developed website for the Corporate Customer for applying the RFID Tags (FASTAG).
- · Customer have to fill all the details after filling data, data will move go to directly Admin Team.
- Admin team will check the details if details are right admin will send to bank, if details are wrong admin will reject the form and form will go to Ops team.
- Ops team will contact that person and edit the details of the customer and etc.

# **Projects**

#### Student Marks Prediction

lune 2019 to Oct. 2019

July 2018 to July 2018

- Technology Used: Python (Machine Learning and Data Science).
- Project is developed for the Student and Teacher. Both of them can analyzed marks before Exam
- · There is some parameter that on that basis student can evaluate themselves
- Student can know house many hours to do study

#### IndNX 4.0 Technology Used: Html and CSS | Bootstrap

- These is a website for the Hackathon.
- Student have register for Hackathon in these website.
- In the website student will get the information of the Hackathon.

#### **KLATHRATE** Aug. 2018 to Aug. 2018

- Technology Used: Html and CSS | Bootstrap.
- The website base on the Share Market and Mutual Funds.
- In these website people will get all the details of Shares and which Shares have to buy or sell information will get on the website
- Mutual Funds details will be seen on the screen which is good or bad

# Activities

Attended Alexa workshop at Techfest IIT Bombay.

Attended Robotics workshop at Techfest IIT Bombay.

Attended AIML workshop at Techniche IIT Guwahati.

Attended Ethical Hacking workshop at Techfest IIT Bombay.

# Certification

Unisoft Technologies - Java SE 8 Programming

Fireblaze · Data Science

Fireblaze · Machine learning

Unisoft TechnologiesC++